export const modalsQuiz = {
  title: 'English Lesson Test - Modal Verbs and Expressions',
  questions: [
    {
      questionText: 'She _______ prepare for her exams.',
      options: ['should', 'must to', 'have to'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      questionText: 'I _______ be home by 10 p.m. as my parents are strict.',
      options: ['should', 'must', 'have to'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      questionText:
        "It's raining heavily. You _______ take an umbrella with you.",
      options: ['had better', 'must', 'had better not'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      questionText: "It's too late. We _______ have left earlier.",
      options: ['had better', 'should', 'must'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      questionText: 'You _______ be quiet in the library.',
      options: ['had better', 'have to', 'must'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
    {
      questionText: 'He _____(not) waste his time on video games.',
      options: ["shouldn't", "mustn't", "doesn't have to"],
      correctAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      questionText: "It's time she _____(learn) how to cook.",
      options: ['learned', 'learns', 'has learned'],
      correctAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      questionText: 'You _____(not) worry so much about your grades.',
      options: ["shouldn't", "mustn't", "don't have to"],
      correctAnswer: 0,
    },
    {
      questionText: 'They _____(complete) the assignment before the deadline.',
      options: ['should', 'have to', 'must'],
      correctAnswer: 1,
    },
    {
      questionText: 'She _____(follow) the rules in the laboratory.',
      options: ['should', 'has to', 'must'],
      correctAnswer: 2,
    },
  ],
};
